AD.MC.016
AbuDhabi
Komunidad: Filipinos in the UAE
2015-2016
AD.MC.016
AbuDhabi
1.0 Linear feet
Xyza, Bacani, Ms
Digital photographs; Dubai, United Arab Emirates; Filipino community; Immigration; Manila, Philippines; Nueva Ecija, Philippines; NYU Abu Dhabi; Philippines; Taguig, Philippines; Work; Workers
- Judjet at an inspection, NYUAD, November 2015; Xyza, Bacani, Ms (Object AD-MC-016_ref1_m)
  Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Digital photographs; Filipino community; Immigration; NYU Abu Dhabi; Work
- Portrait of Judjet inside the car park, November 2015; Xyza, Bacani, Ms (Object AD-MC-016_ref2_m)
- Judjet with the workers during an inspection, November 2015; Xyza, Bacani, Ms (Object AD-MC-016_ref3_m)
- Judjet at an inspection, NYUAD, November 2015; Xyza, Bacani, Ms (Object AD-MC-016_ref4_m)
- Judjet is having lunch with Filipino colleagues, NYUAD, November 2015; Xyza, Bacani, Ms (Object AD-MC-016_ref5_m)
- Filipino migrant workers inside a mall in Abu Dhabi during their day off, November 2015; Xyza, Bacani, Ms (Object AD-MC-016_ref7_m)
  Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Digital photographs; Filipino community; Immigration; NYU Abu Dhabi; Restaurants
- Friday Church service in St. Joseph's Cathedral, Abu Dhabi, November 2015; Xyza, Bacani, Ms (Object AD-MC-016_ref10_m)
  Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Churches; Digital photographs; Filipino community; Immigration
- Catholics line up to receive the holy communion, St. Joseph's Cathedral, Abu Dhabi, November 2015; Xyza, Bacani, Ms (Object AD-MC-016_ref11_m)
- Judjet after the mass in St. Joseph's Cathedral, Abu Dhabi, November 2015; Xyza, Bacani, Ms (Object AD-MC-016_ref12_m)
- Judjet's wall at home, Abu Dhabi, November 2015; Xyza, Bacani, Ms (Object AD-MC-016_ref13_m)
  Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Digital photographs; Filipino community; Immigration
- Filipino migrant workers drink together after a busy day at work., November 2015; Xyza, Bacani, Ms (Object AD-MC-016_ref14_m)
  Digital photographs; Drinking; Dubai, United Arab Emirates; Filipino community; Immigration
- Amber and Jonathan, Dubai, November 2015; Xyza, Bacani, Ms (Object AD-MC-016_ref15_m)
  Digital photographs; Dubai, United Arab Emirates; Filipino community; Immigration
- Claire prepares breakfast, Dubai, November 2015; Xyza, Bacani, Ms (Object AD-MC-016_ref16_m)
  Digital photographs; Dubai, United Arab Emirates; Filipino community; Food; Immigration
- Typical Filipino food, November 2015; Xyza, Bacani, Ms (Object AD-MC-016_ref17_m)
- Migrant workers buy fish in Deira, Dubai, November 2015; Xyza, Bacani, Ms (Object AD-MC-016_ref18_m)
- Claire eats dinner with her family in Dubai, November 2015; Xyza, Bacani, Ms (Object AD-MC-016_ref19_m)
  Digital photographs; Dubai, United Arab Emirates; Family; Filipino community; Immigration
- Claire plays with her daughter Amber, who just arrived in Dubai., November 2015; Xyza, Bacani, Ms (Object AD-MC-016_ref20_m)
  Children; Digital photographs; Dubai, United Arab Emirates; Filipino community; Immigration
- Claire and Jonathan Onte inside their flat, Dubai, November 2015; Xyza, Bacani, Ms (Object AD-MC-016_ref21_m)
- Portrait of Jonathan Onte, Dubai, November 2015; Xyza, Bacani, Ms (Object AD-MC-016_ref22_m)
  Digital photographs; Dubai, United Arab Emirates; Filipino community; Immigration; Individual Portraits
- Amber watches cartoons on her phone. Dubai, November 2015; Xyza, Bacani, Ms (Object AD-MC-016_ref23_m)
  Children; Digital photographs; Dubai, United Arab Emirates; Filipino community; Immigration; Telephones
- Claire, Dubai, November 2015; Xyza, Bacani, Ms (Object AD-MC-016_ref24_m)
- A basketball match, November 2015; Xyza, Bacani, Ms (Object AD-MC-016_ref25_m)
  Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Digital photographs; Filipino community; Immigration; NYU Abu Dhabi; Sports
- Filipino migrants workers inside the Philippine Embassy, Abu Dhabi, November 2015; Xyza, Bacani, Ms (Object AD-MC-016_ref28_m)
  Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Digital photographs; Embassies; Filipino community; Immigration
- Inside the Philippine Embassy in Abu Dhabi, November 2015; Xyza, Bacani, Ms (Object AD-MC-016_ref29_m)
- Consultation and activities are offered in the Embassy, Abu Dhabi, November 2015; Xyza, Bacani, Ms (Object AD-MC-016_ref30_m)
- Mark's youngest son is playing inside their home in Manila, Philippines., December 2015; Xyza, Bacani, Ms (Object AD-MC-016_ref34_m)
  Digital photographs; Filipino community; Immigration; Manila, Philippines
- Mark Anthony Enriquez and his family inside their home in Manila, December 2015; Xyza, Bacani, Ms (Object AD-MC-016_ref35_m)
  Digital photographs; Family; Filipino community; Immigration; Manila, Philippines
- Christmas decorations displayed inside the Enriquez home in Manila, Philippines., December 2015; Xyza, Bacani, Ms (Object AD-MC-016_ref36_m)
  Christmas Trees; Digital photographs; Filipino community; Immigration; Manila, Philippines
- Catholic icons displayed inside the Enriquez home in Manila, Philippines, December 2015; Xyza, Bacani, Ms (Object AD-MC-016_ref37_m)
- Portrait of Mark Enriquez in Manila, Philippines, December 2015; Xyza, Bacani, Ms (Object AD-MC-016_ref38_m)
- Mark's neighborhood in Manila, Philippines, December 2015; Xyza, Bacani, Ms (Object AD-MC-016_ref39_m)
- Filipino migrant workers leaving the country say goodbye to their families at the Manila airport., January 2016; Xyza, Bacani, Ms (Object AD-MC-016_ref50_m)
  Digital photographs; Filipino community; Immigration; Manila, Philippines; Philippines
- View from Judjet's family home in Taguig, Philippines, December 2015; Xyza, Bacani, Ms (Object AD-MC-016_ref51_m)
  Digital photographs; Filipino community; Immigration; Philippines; Taguig, Philippines
- Judjet in the bedroom, Taguig, Philippines, December 2015; Xyza, Bacani, Ms (Object AD-MC-016_ref52_m)
- Judjet with his mother as they watch Judget's daughter play inside their home in Taguig, Philippines, December 2015; Xyza, Bacani, Ms (Object AD-MC-016_ref53_m)
- Judjet's family home, Taguig, Philippines, December 2015; Xyza, Bacani, Ms (Object AD-MC-016_ref54_m)
- Judjet spends time with his neighbors, Taguig, Philippines, December 2015; Xyza, Bacani, Ms (Object AD-MC-016_ref55_m)
- Judjet's daughter playing, December 2015; Xyza, Bacani, Ms (Object AD-MC-016_ref56_m)
  Children; Digital photographs; Filipino community; Girls; Immigration; Philippines; Taguig, Philippines
- Judjet with his phone. Mementos on the wall, December 2015; Xyza, Bacani, Ms (Object AD-MC-016_ref57_m)
  Digital photographs; Filipino community; Immigration; Philippines; Taguig, Philippines; Telephones
- Judjet fixes the door while his mother prepares lunch in their family home. Philippines, December 2015; Xyza, Bacani, Ms (Object AD-MC-016_ref58_m)
- Judjet in the Philippines, December 2015; Xyza, Bacani, Ms (Object AD-MC-016_ref59_m)
  Digital photographs; Filipino community; Girls; Immigration; Philippines; Taguig, Philippines